(Raj:)Turns out, total sweetheart.
(Claire:)Okay, but you and I have been
keeping things casual.
(Claire:)Uh, will you introduce me
as your friend
(Claire:)or as your girlfriend?
(Claire:)What if I like them
(Claire:)and they don't like me?
(Claire:)What if they like me
and I don't like them?
(Raj:)Boy, it wasn't this hard
with Bon Jovi.
I said, “You rock,”
he said, “Thanks, man,”
(Raj:)and that was that.
(sniffs)
(Penny:)Hey, you ready to go?
(Leonard:)Hang on.
What are you doing?
(Leonard:)Oh, I found a scratch-and-sniff
book about wine tasting.
(Leonard:)It teaches the different
flavor notes to look for.
(Penny:)You actually smell the wine?
(Leonard:)I mostly just smell
my nasal spray.
(Penny:)Are your sinuses acting up?
(Leonard:)Since my preschool got a bunny.
(Penny:)Hey, are you still hanging out
with Bernadette tonight?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And we're going to prove
that we don't need alcohol
(Sheldon:)to enjoy ourselves.
(Penny:)Oh, good for you.
(Sheldon:)Or caffeine, tobacco, sushi,
(Sheldon:)soft cheese, processed meats
and Jacuzzis,